Lesson 25.
第25课。
The Kuddy Sark, one of the most famous sailing ships of the 19th century.
Kuddy Sark是19世纪最著名的帆船之一。
The Kuddy Sark, can still be seen at Greewich.
萨克（Sark）仍然可以在格林威治（Greenwich）看到。
She stands on dry land and is visited by thousands of people each year.
她站在干旱的土地上，每年有成千上万的人拜访。
impressive: adj. 给人深刻印象的
She serves as an impressive reminder of the great ships of past before they were replaced
在替换之前，她令人印象深刻地想起了过去的巨大船只
by.
经过。
Steam ships.
蒸汽船。
vessel: n.   轮船，大木船
Sailing vessels like the Kuddy Sark were used to carry tea from China and wool from Australia.
诸如Kuddy Sark之类的帆船被用来从中国和澳大利亚的羊毛中携带茶。
The Kuddy Sark was one of the fastest sailing ships that has ever been built.
萨克（Sark）是有史以来最快的帆船之一。
The only other ship to match her was the Thermopoly.
唯一与她相匹配的另一艘船是热门。
Both these ships set out from Shanghai on June 18, 1872 on an exciting race to England.
这两艘船于1872年6月18日从上海出发，参加了一场激动人心的英格兰比赛。
This race, which went on for exactly four exactly four months, was the last of its kind.
这场比赛恰好四个月持续了四个月，这是最后一场比赛。
It marked the end of the great tradition of ships with sails and the beginning of a new
它标志着帆船的伟大传统的终结和新的
era: n.   时期，时代
era.
时代。
Java: n.   爪哇（印度尼西亚一岛）
The first of the two ships to reach Java after the race had begun was the Thermopoly.
比赛开始后，两艘船到达Java的第一艘船中的第一艘是热门。
But on the Indian Ocean, the Kuddy Sark took lead.
但是在印度洋，萨克（Sark）王位领先。
It seemed certain that she would be the first ship home.
似乎可以肯定的是她将是第一艘船。
But during the race she had a lot of bad luck.
但是在比赛中，她有很多厄运。
In August, she was struck by a very heavy storm during which her rudder was torn away.
八月，她被一场非常严重的暴风雨击中，在那儿，她的舵被撕开了。
roll: v.   颠簸，摇摆, steer: v.   掌握方向
The Kuddy Sark rolled from side to side and it became impossible to steer her.
那个狂热的萨克从一侧到另一侧滚动，无法引导她。
temporary: adj. 临时的, plank: n.   大块木板, fit: v.   安装
A temporary rudder was made on board from spare planks and it was fitted with great difficulty.
用备用木板在船上制作了一个临时的舵，并遇到了很大的困难。
This greatly reduced the speed of the ship.
这大大降低了船的速度。
For there was a danger that if she traveled too quickly, this rudder would be torn away
因为有一个危险，如果她旅行得太快，那么这个舵将被撕掉
as well.
也
Because of this, the Kuddy Sark lost her lead.
因此，Sark的罪魁祸首失去了领先。
fit: v.   安装
After crossing the equator, the captain called in at a port to have a new rudder fitted.
越过赤道后，船长在港口呼唤安装了一个新的舵。
But by now the Thermopoly was over 500 miles ahead.
但是到目前为止，热区已超过500英里。
fit: v.   安装
Though the new rudder was fitted at tremendous speed, it was impossible for the Kuddy Sark to
尽管新的舵以极高的速度安装了，但Kuddy Sark不可能
win.
赢。
She arrived in England a week after the Thermopoly.
热门一周后，她到达英格兰。
delay: n.   耽误
Even this was remarkable, considering that she had had so many delays.
考虑到她有很多延误，这也非常了不起。
Jesus no doubt that if she had not lost her rudder she would have won the race easily.
耶稣毫无疑问，如果她没有失去舵，她会很容易赢得比赛。